{
    "id": "85c2b1cd8eca453b95d69f4a7f3bd728",
    "title": "Using otherwise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "edb16059f63a4c40a417701f6c8c2035",
            "title": "If, Otherwise, Unless",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We must hurry up .................................. we will miss the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "otherwise",
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... we do not hurry up, we will miss the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... we hurry up, we will miss the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You must work hard ....................................., you will fail the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "if",
                        "otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... you do not work hard, you will fail the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "Otherwise",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... you work hard, you will fail the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "If",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are in love with him. Why do you want to pretend .......................................?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hope she mends her ways. ........................................., she will be sacked.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The vaccine has saved tens of thousands of children who would ................................... have died.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "Unless",
                        "otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Of course she is interested in him. ............................................., she wouldnâ€™t be asking about his whereabouts.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Otherwise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}